I talk to them in Marathi language,  because here
so many of them don´t understand any other language but Marathi.
Today is the day of Gauri Puja.
Gauri is the one who, as a Virgin, created Shri Ganesha.
And in the same pattern you have got your realization.
In the same pattern!
So you have to use the same power within you that is of Gauri,
that you keep your heart clean. You must have a clean heart.
You must have a clean thinking.
There should be purity in your mind.
Of course, the bhakti does  give that purity,
but if there is anything lingering in your mind
I have to tell you there are three things
that are going to happen from today.
First, we have started Vishwa Nirmala Dharma.
You are under the
vision of Shri Ganesh,
under the guidance of your Spirit,
and under the blessings of God Almighty.
But be careful, because once you become that,
you have to keep to that Dharma, you have to be honest about it.
If you are dishonest from today onwards
you be careful, anything can happen to you
if you get out of the maryadas.
Till you keep the maryadas of Sahaja Yoga, saying morning,
evening, night that: “I am a Sahaja Yogi”,
nobody can harm you, hurt you. Nobody can trouble you.
On the contrary you will be enjoying life
if you keep to the maryadas.
But if you leave the maryadas of Sahaja Yoga,
you will have big problems.
So this is the second thing I want to tell you
that today we have started the great vision,
which was promised long time back of realized souls.
Now the third is that
with all these things we are doing,
we must promise to God also
that we will know about Sahaja Yoga,
through proper understanding, reading every word of it.
We'll master the knowledge of Sahaja Yoga.
We’ll keep ourselves clean.
And completely surrender our lives to Sahaja Yoga.
This is what you have to promise in your heart.
Surrendering to Sahaja Yoga is actually surrendering to joy,
bliss and peace.
In that you are the gainer, nobody is a loser in it.
This is how today we have to decide once for all.
Today is the day as you know, my forefathers
called it the first day of the year(*).
and they have the kailasha and the shawl of the Goddess
as the emblem
or you can call it as a flag of Shalivahan.
In any way my delay is important because
trước đó là ngày Amavasya (ngày cuối cùng của tuần trăng tối),
và chúng ta phải thoát khỏi ngày Amavasya đó để ngày đầu tiên bắt đầu.
Đó là lý do tại sao có sự chậm trễ,
có kẹt xe, mọi thứ đều được sắp đặt.
Chúng ta không nên lo lắng: “Tại sao lại có sự chậm trễ, tại sao lại có chuyện này?”
Đôi khi Ta có thể đến sớm hơn, Ta có thể đến muộn hơn, tất cả đều được sắp đặt.
Bởi vì trong ngày Amavasya làm sao các con có thể làm lễ puja cho Ta được?
Chuyện đơn giản là vậy. Mọi thứ đều được sắp đặt, mọi thứ đều được tính toán.
Mọi thứ đều ổn, chỉ cần là chính mình.
Đừng buồn bực vì bất cứ điều gì, đừng lo lắng hay bất cứ điều gì.
Chỉ cần cố gắng giữ sự bình yên tuyệt đối.
Ta sẽ cho các con một vài bài kiểm tra bằng cách xem
các con giữ được tình trạng đó đến mức nào,
tình trạng hoàn toàn bình yên trong nội tâm.
Nếu các con không làm gì sai, nếu các con là một hành giả Sahaja,
thì sẽ không có sự xáo trộn nào cả.
Nếu người khác làm sai, cũng không sao,
không thành vấn đề, các con đã không làm gì sai cả
Miễn là các con không làm gì sai thì không có gì phải lo lắng.
Và thực tế là, ngay cả khi các con đã làm điều gì đó sai trái,
Thượng đế luôn ở đó để tha thứ cho các con.
Vì vậy, đừng lo lắng gì cả. Hãy có tất cả sức mạnh,
có tất cả lòng can đảm và tiến bước với lời hứa này.
Bởi vì Ta thấy bây giờ Sahaja Yoga sẽ có một bước ngoặt mới.
Chắc chắn là như vậy.
Chúng ta sẽ đi đến một giai đoạn
nơi hàng ngàn hàng ngàn người sẽ chung tay.
Nhưng trước hết những người là nền tảng,
những người đầu tiên
phải nỗ lực rất nhiều để giữ mình vượt lên trên
tất cả những cám dỗ ngu ngốc
tất cả những điều ngu ngốc mà các con đã và đang làm,
những điều đó là asahaja (không phải Sahaja).
Ngôn ngữ phải ngọt ngào, hành vi của các con phải tốt đẹp,
phải rất nhẹ nhàng và mềm mỏng.
Các con nên di chuyển như một yogi, sống như một vị thánh,
và mọi người sẽ thấy được sự vĩ đại của Sahaja Yoga thông qua các con.
Cầu xin Thượng đế ban phước cho các con